ryu-anime.com 2017-03-19

# Privacy Policy - RyuAnime - Dubbed Anime / Subbed Anime

**What information do we collect?**

Protecting the privacy of RyuAnime's visitors is very important to us. We here at RyuAnime are committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. RyuAnime and its staff will never ask for any personal information (other than, but not limited to, username/email when leaving a comment. You can, however, leave a completely anonymous username/email). 

**Video Disclaimer**

No video content is held on our servers and we, along with our staff, are in no way affiliated with the video content. The video content that is displayed originates from online video streaming websites, such as, but not limited to Dailymotion, Yourupload, MyspaceTV, Veoh, Putlocker, etc. 

**Copyright Infringement**

_In case of copyright infringement, please directly contact the responsible parties._ RyuAnime operates as an index and database of Anime content found publicly available on the internet, in principle conducting in the same way as any of the large search engines, such as Google, Bing and Yahoo. However, RyuAnime and its staff strongly believe in the protection of intellectual property and would be willing to assist when possible and applicable. If you believe a link should be removed from the website, and have already contacted the responsible parties regarding the video(s), then please contact us directly. 

Users who upload to the video streaming websites mentioned above agree not to upload illegal content when creating their user accounts. RyuAnime does not accept responsibility for content hosted on third party websites, nor do we upload videos ourselves or encourage others to do so. The videos are streamed directly from the third-party video sharing services. 

**Does RyuAnime use cookies?**

As most websites on the internet, yes. For those of you who are unaware, cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. RyuAnime use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools for users in the future. 

**Advertising**

RyuAnime uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may compile data (not including any personal information) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. 

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline. 

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy. 

**Changes to our Privacy Policy** RyuAnime reserves the right to make any changes to our Privacy Policy, at any time. If and when we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, with an update that can be viewed site-wide.
